

Md Ashraf Ali

Sr.Graphic Designer

Profile

Hello! My name is Ashraf, in the graphic design industry with more than 6 years working experience in various companies. I am ready to work with companies to create the best graphic design projects for corporate business. To succeed in an environment of growth and excellence and earn a job which provides me



Portfolio link

https://www.behance.net/gallery/1 21328357/My-Project

Education

Ambedkar Open University 2015 - 2017

B.com

Svn SSC 2012 - 2013

Ssc 10th class

Software

- Photoshop
- CorelDRAW
- Illustrator
- Adobe Premiere Pro
- After effects

Work Experience

Senior Graphic Designer Adweta digital Solutions | 2020 - present

Work closely with the marketing team and creative team to improve the quality of the company's weekly social media posts . Video editings when needed and print work

Graphic Designer Eiffel | 2019 - 2020

Creating graphic design works for company publication and marketing purposes under the guidance of Management

Graphic Designer Anmol Media Service | 2018 - 2019

Creating graphic design works for company publication and marketing purposes under the guidance of Management



